<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Talks on </title>
    <link>https://bwoodfork.github.io/talks/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Talks on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Byron Woodfork</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 18 Nov 2018 02:13:50 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://bwoodfork.github.io/talks/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Mid-Career Survival Tips for POC</title>
      <link>https://bwoodfork.github.io/talks/mid-career-survival-tips-for-people-of-color-in-tech/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Nov 2018 02:13:50 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bwoodfork.github.io/talks/mid-career-survival-tips-for-people-of-color-in-tech/</guid>
      <description>Abstract Figuring out what it is you want to do or what sort of company you want to work for in the middle of your career is a tough task. Juggling that with the obstacles that we face as people of color in tech can make things seem pretty overwhelming. This talk is directed to aid those in the middle of their careers figure out a path forward through aligning their values with their company, finding mentorship and getting paid what they&amp;rsquo;re worth.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Truth About Mentoring Minorities</title>
      <link>https://bwoodfork.github.io/talks/the-truth-about-mentoring-minorities/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Nov 2018 02:13:50 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bwoodfork.github.io/talks/the-truth-about-mentoring-minorities/</guid>
      <description>Video  Abstract One of the most effective ways to battle our industry&amp;rsquo;s lack of inclusion, diversity, and job retention is developing quality mentors to help aid minorities throughout their careers. In the tech industry, we currently lack the ability to produce mentors who are able to effectively teach and connect with their minority protégés. It&amp;rsquo;s because of this that minorities are feeling excluded at work and are unable to climb up the corporate ladder at the same pace as their non-minority protégés.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Talk Panel: Growing the clojure community</title>
      <link>https://bwoodfork.github.io/talks/growing-the-clojure-community/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Jan 2000 02:13:50 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bwoodfork.github.io/talks/growing-the-clojure-community/</guid>
      <description> Video  Abstract Let’s come together and discuss how we can attract more people to programming in general and Clojure specifically. Learn strategies that you can use to build the Clojure in your backyard and beyond.
Where this talk was given  Opening keynote for SelfConference  </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>